{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1584","name":"U Of D Jesuit High School","address":"8400 S Cambridge St","zipcode":"48221","owner":"U Of D Jesuit High School","licenseNumber":"035843","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Non-Public School","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"210","coords":"-83.15417,42.43284","geojson":{"id":"1584","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.154167333,42.432836714]},"properties":{"name":"U Of D Jesuit High School","owner":"U Of D Jesuit High School","address":"8400 S Cambridge St","zipcode":"48221","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"Medium","license_number":"035843","establishmentid":"1584","establishment_type":"Non-Public School","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"210","most_recent_license_date":null}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"4452","name":"Happy's Pizza #100","address":"7731 E Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48234"},{"establishmentid":"1081","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken ","address":"8939 W Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"5078","name":"Papa's Pizza - JNL Pizzaria, Inc.","address":"7410 W Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"520","name":"Tom's Tavern","address":"10093 W Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"1120","name":"John J Bagley Elementary School","address":"8100 Curtis St","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"1869","name":"Little Caesar's Pizza #24","address":"10200 W Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"400","name":"Deli-Plaza Inc","address":"18401 Wyoming Ave","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"825","name":"Bates Academy","address":"19701 Wyoming Ave","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"5428","name":"BabyBack's Open Pit","address":"7108 W Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"3564","name":"Chef Gree's Soul N The Wall ","address":"10009 Curtis St","zipcode":"48221"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"49052","inspectionDate":"2019-09-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-09-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly date marked","subProblem":"Longer than 7 days stored at 41 degrees f","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-09-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-09-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-302.12","violationDescription":"Except for containers holding FOOD that can be readily and unmistakably recognized such as dry pasta, working containers holding FOOD or FOOD ingredients that are removed from their original packages for use in the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, such as cooking oils, flour, herbs, potato flakes, salt, spices, and sugar shall be identified with the common name of the FOOD.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not identified","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Shelf","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-09-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-09-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"MFL289.4119","violationDescription":"Sec. 4119. (1) Except as otherwise provided in subsection (2), a person licensed as a food establishment under this chapter shall keep a copy of the current license or temporary license furnished by the department posted and exposed in a conspicuous place for public inspection. A conspicuous place is the principal place where food business is transacted.  (2) In the case of vending machines, the name and address and telephone number of the current vending machine location operator shall be conspicuously displayed on each vending machine.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"displayed","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"44203","inspectionDate":"2018-11-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-603.16","violationDescription":"Washed UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT shall be rinsed so that abrasives are removed and cleaning chemicals are removed or diluted through the use of water or a detergent-SANITIZER solution by APPROVED procedures.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Washed equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not rinsed","subProblem":"After washing and before sanitizing","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Meat slicer","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2018-11-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-302.12","violationDescription":"Except for containers holding FOOD that can be readily and unmistakably recognized such as dry pasta, working containers holding FOOD or FOOD ingredients that are removed from their original packages for use in the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, such as cooking oils, flour, herbs, potato flakes, salt, spices, and sugar shall be identified with the common name of the FOOD.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not identified","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Shelf","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2018-11-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."}]},{"inspectionid":"39887","inspectionDate":"2017-03-22T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.111","violationDescription":"If immersion in hot water is used for SANITIZING in a manual operation, the temperature of the water shall be maintained at 171 F or above. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Manual warewash sanitizing solution temperature","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than 170 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"THREE COMPARTMENT SINK","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-03-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace booster heater."},{"violationCode":"3-501.18","violationDescription":"A FOOD specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A) or (B) shall be discarded if it:  \r\n    (1) Exceeds the temperature and time combination specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A),              except time that the product is frozen; (P)\r\n    (2) Is in a container or PACKAGE that does not bear a date or day; (P) or\r\n    (3) Is appropriately marked with a date or day that exceeds a temperature and              time combination as specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A). (P)  \r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready to eat, potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Beyond consume by date","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Dispose of food item."},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-03-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Relocate."}]},{"inspectionid":"36863","inspectionDate":"2016-10-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-202.13","violationDescription":"An air gap between the water supply inlet and the flood level rim of the PLUMBING FIXTURE, EQUIPMENT, or nonFOOD EQUIPMENT shall be at least twice the diameter of the water supply inlet and may not be less than 1 inch. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Air gap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than twice the diameter of supply line","subProblem":"","location":"THREE COMPARTMENT SINK","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2016-11-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide air gap that is twice the diameter of the drain line and no less than 1 inch."},{"violationCode":"3-601.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be offered for human consumption in a way that does not mislead or misinform the CONSUMER.   \r\n(B) FOOD or COLOR ADDITIVES, colored overwraps, or lights may not be used to misrepresent the true appearance, color, or quality of a FOOD.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Misrepresentation of food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"By service that","subProblem":"Misinforms consumer","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2016-10-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discontinue."},{"violationCode":"3-601.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be offered for human consumption in a way that does not mislead or misinform the CONSUMER.   \r\n(B) FOOD or COLOR ADDITIVES, colored overwraps, or lights may not be used to misrepresent the true appearance, color, or quality of a FOOD.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2016-10-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"With handle in product","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2016-10-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store with handle extended out of product."},{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"ICE BIN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"To prevent contamination of food or food related items","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2016-10-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Relocate."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"ICE BIN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-10-30T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1584"}}